A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, general correspondence, RG 2, 1952-1957 FA425
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1953
  - Poland, 1953; 1953/789
    - Poland, 1953 (Box 46, Folder 298)
  - Spain, 1953; 1953/795
    - Spain, 1953 (Box 46, Folder 299)
    - Spain - Medical Sciences, 1953; 1953/795.A
      - Spain, 1953 (Box 46, Folder 299)
  - Sweden, 1953; 1953/800
    - Sweden - A-Z, 1953 (Box 46, Folder 300)
    - Sweden - A-Z, 1953 (Box 46, Folder 301)
    - Sweden - Medical Sciences, 1953; 1953/800.A
      - Sweden, 1953 (Box 46, Folder 302)
    - Sweden - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1953; 1953/800.E
      - Sweden, 1953 (Box 46, Folder 302)
    - Sweden - Humanities and Arts, 1953; 1953/800.R
      - Sweden, 1953 (Box 46, Folder 302)
    - Sweden - Social Sciences, 1953; 1953/800.S
      - Sweden, 1953 (Box 46, Folder 302)
  - Switzerland, 1953; 1953/803
    - Switzerland, 1953 (Box 46, Folder 303)
    - Switzerland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1953; 1953/803.E
      - Switzerland, 1953 (Box 46, Folder 304)
  - Near East Region, 1953; 1953/804
    - Near East, 1953 (Box 46, Folder 304)
    - Near East Region - Humanities and Arts, 1953; 1953/804.R
      - Marshall, John - "Near East Trip, 1953" (Box 46, Folder 305)
  - Turkey, 1953; 1953/805
    - Turkey, 1953 (Box 47, Folder 306)
    - Turkey - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1953; 1953/805.E
      - Turkey, 1953 (Box 47, Folder 306)
    - Turkey - Humanities and Arts, 1953; 1953/805.R
      - Turkey, 1953 (Box 47, Folder 306)
  - Jordan, 1953; 1953/816
    - Jordan, 1953 (Box 47, Folder 307)
    - Jordan - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1953; 1953/816.E
      - Jordan, 1953 (Box 47, Folder 307)
  - Israel, 1953; 1953/825
    - Israel, 1953 (Box 47, Folder 308)
    - Israel - Medical Sciences, 1953; 1953/825.A
      - Israel, 1953 (Box 47, Folder 308)
    - Israel - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1953; 1953/825.E
      - Israel, 1953 (Box 47, Folder 308)
  - Lebanon, 1953; 1953/833
    - Lebanon - A-H, 1953 (Box 47, Folder 309)
    - Lebanon - I-Z, 1953 (Box 47, Folder 310)
    - Lebanon - Nursing, 1953; 1953/833.C
      - Lebanon, 1953 (Box 47, Folder 310)
    - Lebanon - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1953; 1953/833.E
      - Lebanon, 1953 (Box 47, Folder 310)
    - Lebanon - Malaria, 1953; 1953/833.I
      - Lebanon, 1953 (Box 47, Folder 310)
    - Lebanon - Humanities and Arts, 1953; 1953/833.R
      - Lebanon, 1953 (Box 47, Folder 310)
- General Correspondence, 1954
  - International, 1954; 1954/100
    - Aitken, Thomas H.G. - Publications, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Anderson, Charles R. - Publications, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Anderson, Richard K. - Publications, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Baird, Guy B. - Balfour, Marshall C., 1954 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Barnard, Chester I. - Bauer, J.H. - Beal, J.G. - Bevier, George, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Blanton, Mary Jane - Boyd, Mark F. - Brackett, Elizabeth W. - Bradfield, Richard, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Burgher, John C. - Publications - Burden, Robert P. - Publications, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Carr, Henry F. - Publications, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Carter, J.C. - Cassals, Jordi - Publications, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Causey, Ottis R. - Publications, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Chandler, Robert F. - Chope, H.D. - Clarke, Delphine - Publications, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Cobb, William C. - Congress for Cultural Freedom - Council on Foreign Relations, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Council for International Organizations of Medical Science - D'Arms, Edward F. - Debevoise, Thomas M. - DeVinney, L.C., 1954 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Diplomatic Services - (A-2), 1954 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Downs, Wilbur G. - Publication - Dyer, Brian R., 1954 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Economic - Evans, Roger F., 1954 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Fahs, Charles B., 1954 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Films - Grant, John B., 1954 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Gray, George W. - Hahn, Richard C., 1954 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Harrar, J. George, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Hoyt, Jennifer M. - Intergovernmental Committee for European Migration, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - International - (A-Z), 1954 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Interracial - Johnson, Harald N., 1954 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Johnson, Lillian - Kerr, J. Austin, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Kimball, Lindsley F. - Knipe, Fred W. - Publications, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Kokernot, Robert H. - Publications, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Lambert, Robert A. - Lee, Ivy, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Letort, Robert - Logan, John A. - Publications - Loomis, F.W., 1954 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - McCoy, Oliver R. - McIntosh, William A. - Publications, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - McKelvey, John J. - Magoon, Estus H., 1954 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Maier, John - Publications, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Mailing Lists, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Marshall, John, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Miler, Harry M. - Morison, Robert S., 1954 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Ohlson, Virginia M. - Oliver, Wade W., 1954 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Peterson, O.L. - Rhind, F.M., 1954 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Roberts, L.M. - Rupert, J.A., 1954 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Roberts, L.M. - Rupert, J.A., 1954 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Ruppel, Robert F. - Rusk, Dean, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Russell, Paul F. - 1-5-1954 - 5-31-1954 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Russell, Paul F. - 1-6-1954 - 12-1959 - Publications (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Sasse, Bruce E., 1954 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Smith, Donald L., 1954 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Smith, Hugh H. - Smithburn, K.C. - Publications, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - South Pacific Commission - Strode, George K., 1954 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Struthers, R.R., 1954 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Taylor, Richard M. - Publications, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Tennant, Mary Elizabeth, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Theiler, Max - Thompson, Kenneth - Trapido, Harold, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - United Nations - (A-Malik), 1954 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - United Nations - (Population - Wright), 1954 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - UNESCO, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - UNESCO - (A-L), 1954 (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - UNESCO - (M-Z), 1954 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - United Nations - World Health Organization - (A-Z), 1954 (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - United Nations - World Health Organization - January - May, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - United Nations - World Health Organization - June, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - United Nations - World Health Organization - July - December - VanDyke, George - Warren, Andrew J., 1954 (Box 8, Folder 57)
    - Watson, Robert - January - March, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - Watson, Robert - April - August, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - Watson, Robert - August - December, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - Weaver, Warren - Webb, Vanderbilt, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - Weir, John M. - Publications, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 62)
    - Wellhausen, E.J., 1954 (Box 9, Folder 63)
    - Wells, Clifford W. - Willits, Joseph, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 64)
    - Work, Telford H. - Publications, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 65)
    - World - Yearbook of Education, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 66)
    - International - ( A-Z), 1954 (Box 9, Folder 67)
    - United Nations - International Children's Emergency Fund, 1954 (Box 51, Folder 338)
    - International - Medical Sciences, 1954; 1954/100.A
      - International - ( A-Z), 1954 (Box 9, Folder 67)
    - International - Nursing, 1954; 1954/100.C
      - International - ( A-Z), 1954 (Box 9, Folder 67)
    - International - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1954; 1954/100.E
      - International - ( A-Z), 1954 (Box 9, Folder 67)
      - International - ( A-Z), 1954 (Box 9, Folder 67)
      - International - ( A-Z), 1954 (Box 9, Folder 67)
      - International - ( A-Z), 1954 (Box 9, Folder 67)
      - International - ( A-Z), 1954 (Box 9, Folder 67)
    - International - Natural Sciences Fellows, 1954; 1954/100.ED
      - International - ( A-Z), 1954 (Box 9, Folder 67)
    - International - Humanities Fellows, 1954; 1954/100.ER
      - International - ( A-Z), 1954 (Box 9, Folder 67)
    - International - Social Science Fellows, 1954; 1954/100.ES
      - International - ( A-Z), 1954 (Box 9, Folder 67)
    - International - Medicine and Public Health Fellows, 1954; 1954/100.EY
      - International - ( A-Z), 1954 (Box 9, Folder 67)
    - International - Social Sciences, 1954; 1954/100.S
      - International - ( A-Z), 1954 (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - United States, 1954; 1954/200
    - United States - (AA - America), 1954 (Box 9, Folder 68)
    - United States - American - (A-Bo), 1954 (Box 9, Folder 69)
    - United States - American Bureau for Medical Aid to China, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 70)
    - United States - American - (C), 1954 (Box 10, Folder 71)
    - United States - American - (D-G), 1954 (Box 10, Folder 72)
    - United States - American - (I-M), 1954 (Box 10, Folder 73)
    - United States - American - (N-P), 1954 (Box 10, Folder 74)
    - United States - American - (O-Z), 1954 (Box 11, Folder 75)
    - United States - (Ames, WR & Co - AR), 1954 (Box 11, Folder 76)
    - United States - (Asia - Associated Press), 1954 (Box 11, Folder 77)
    - United States - Associated Research Councils, 1954 (Box 11, Folder 78)
    - United States - Associated Universities - Augustana, 1954 (Box 11, Folder 79)
    - United States - (Ba-Bar), 1954 (Box 11, Folder 80)
    - United States - (Bau-Bio), 1954 (Box 12, Folder 81)
    - United States - (Bis-Bronx), 1954 (Box 12, Folder 82)
    - United States - Brookings Institute - (January - March), 1954 (Box 12, Folder 83)
    - United States - Brookings Institute - (May - December), 1954 (Box 12, Folder 84)
    - United States - (Brooklyn - Burton), 1954 (Box 12, Folder 85)
    - United States - (Ca-Carlson), 1954 (Box 12, Folder 86)
    - United States - Carnegie - (C-E), 1954 (Box 12, Folder 87)
    - United States - Carnegie Institute - Carnegie Institution of Washington - French, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 88)
    - United States - Carnegie Institute - Fine Arts, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 89)
    - United States - (Cartier-Clough), 1954 (Box 13, Folder 90)
    - United States - (Cof-Colgate), 1954 (Box 13, Folder 91)
    - United States - (Coll-Colo), 1954 (Box 13, Folder 92)
    - United States - Columbia University - (A-F), 1954 (Box 13, Folder 93)
    - United States - Columbia University - (G-W), 1954 (Box 13, Folder 94)
    - United States - (Com), 1954 (Box 14, Folder 95)
    - United States - (Con - Cornell College), 1954 (Box 14, Folder 96)
    - United States - Cornell University, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 97)
    - United States - (Cos-Cus), 1954 (Box 14, Folder 98)
    - United States - (Da-Do), 1954 (Box 14, Folder 99)
    - United States - (Dr-Dy), 1954 (Box 14, Folder 100)
    - United States - (E), 1954 (Box 14, Folder 101)
    - United States - (Fa-Foo), 1954 (Box 15, Folder 102)
    - United States - Ford Foundation, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 103)
    - United States - (Ford Motor - Fox), 1954 (Box 15, Folder 104)
    - United States - (Fr), 1954 (Box 15, Folder 105)
    - United States - (Fu), 1954 (Box 15, Folder 106)
    - United States - (Ga-Gol), 1954 (Box 15, Folder 107)
    - United States - (Goo-Gu), 1954 (Box 16, Folder 108)
    - United States - (Hackett-Hartford), 1954 (Box 16, Folder 109)
    - United States - Harvard University - (A-B), 1954 (Box 16, Folder 110)
    - United States - Harvard University - (C-H), 1954 (Box 16, Folder 111)
    - United States - Harvard University - (I-N), 1954 (Box 16, Folder 112)
    - United States - Harvard University - (O-School of Public Health), 1954 (Box 16, Folder 113)
    - United States - Harvard University - (School of Public Health), 1954 (Box 16, Folder 114)
    - United States - Harvard University - (Social-White), 1954 (Box 17, Folder 115)
    - United States - (Harvard - Yenching - HEA), 1954 (Box 17, Folder 116)
    - United States - (Heb-Hew), 1954 (Box 17, Folder 117)
    - United States - (Hi-Ho), 1954 (Box 17, Folder 118)
    - United States - (Hu-Hy), 1954 (Box 17, Folder 119)
    - United States - (I-Indiana), 1954 (Box 17, Folder 120)
    - United States - Industrial Council for Tropical Health, 1954 (Box 17, Folder 121)
    - United States - (Industrial Relations - Institute of Public Administration), 1954 (Box 17, Folder 122)
    - United States - (Ins-IV), 1954 (Box 18, Folder 123)
    - United States - (J), 1954 (Box 18, Folder 124)
    - United States - (Ka-Kee), 1954 (Box 18, Folder 125)
    - United States - Kellogg Foundation, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 126)
    - United States - (Ken-Kre), 1954 (Box 18, Folder 127)
    - United States - (La-Library of Congress), 1954 (Box 18, Folder 128)
    - United States - (Library Journal-Lyric), 1954 (Box 18, Folder 129)
    - United States - (Mc), 1954 (Box 19, Folder 130)
    - United States - (Mabry-Mary Knoll), 1954 (Box 19, Folder 131)
    - United States - (Marvyama-Mayo), 1954 (Box 19, Folder 132)
    - United States - (Mea-Meh), 1954 (Box 19, Folder 133)
    - United States - (Mellen-Midd), 1954 (Box 19, Folder 134)
    - United States - (Midk-Monte), 1954 (Box 19, Folder 135)
    - United States - (Montg-My), 1954 (Box 19, Folder 136)
    - United States - (Nadel-National Book Committee), 1954 (Box 20, Folder 137)
    - United States - National - (C), 1954 (Box 20, Folder 138)
    - United States - National - (D-I), 1954 (Box 20, Folder 139)
    - United States - National - (L-P), 1954 (Box 20, Folder 140)
    - United States - National Research Council - (A-Z), 1954 (Box 20, Folder 141)
    - United States - National - (S-V), 1954 (Box 20, Folder 142)
    - United States - National - (S-V), 1954 (Box 20, Folder 142)
    - United States - (Ne-New York Public Library), 1954 (Box 21, Folder 143)
    - United States - (New York Society-Newton), 1954 (Box 21, Folder 144)
    - United States - (Nolte-Nyos), 1954 (Box 21, Folder 145)
    - United States - (O), 1954 (Box 21, Folder 146)
    - United States - (Pac-Pah), 1954 (Box 21, Folder 147)
    - United States - Pan American - (A-U), 1954 (Box 21, Folder 148)
    - NOT USED, 1954 (Box 21, Folder 149)
    - United States - (Pap-Par), 1954 (Box 21, Folder 150)
    - United States - (Pau-Pin), 1954 (Box 22, Folder 151)
    - United States - (Pit-Princetonpolychrome), 1954 (Box 22, Folder 152)
    - United States - Princeton University - (A-W), 1954 (Box 22, Folder 153)
    - United States - (Pr-Q), 1954 (Box 22, Folder 154)
    - United States - (Ra-Rob), 1954 (Box 22, Folder 155)
    - United States - Rochester Regional Hospital Council, 1954 (Box 22, Folder 156)
    - United States - (ROCHLIN-Rocky), 1954 (Box 23, Folder 157)
    - United States - (Rod-Roz), 1954 (Box 23, Folder 158)
    - United States - (Ru), 1954 (Box 23, Folder 159)
    - United States - (Sa-Sev), 1954 (Box 23, Folder 160)
    - United States - (Sa-Sev), 1954 (Box 23, Folder 161)
    - United States - Slavic Studies Joint Committee, 1954 (Box 23, Folder 162)
    - United States - Slavic Studies Joint Committee, 1954 (Box 24, Folder 163)
    - United States - Slavic Studies Joint Committee, 1954 (Box 24, Folder 164)
    - United States - (Slo-So), 1954 (Box 24, Folder 165)
    - United States - (Sp-Sq), 1954 (Box 24, Folder 166)
    - United States - (St-Sw), 1954 (Box 24, Folder 167)
    - United States - (T), 1954 (Box 24, Folder 168)
    - United States - (Um-United States), 1954 (Box 24, Folder 169)
    - United States - U.S. - (Agriculture-Atomic), 1954 (Box 24, Folder 170)
    - United States - U.S. - (C-Fe), 1954 (Box 25, Folder 171)
    - United States - U.S. - Foreign Operations Administration, 1954 (Box 25, Folder 172)
    - United States - U.S. - (H-J), 1954 (Box 25, Folder 173)
    - United States - U.S. - (L-O), 1954 (Box 25, Folder 174)
    - United States - U.S. - Public Health Service - (A-F), 1954 (Box 25, Folder 175)
    - United States - U.S. - Public Health Service - (A-Z), 1954 (Box 25, Folder 176)
    - United States - U.S. - State (A-Z), 1954 (Box 25, Folder 177)
    - United States - U.S. - State - (A-Z), 1954 (Box 25, Folder 177)
    - United States - (U.S. Senate - Upjohn), 1954 (Box 25, Folder 178)
    - United States - University - (A-California), 1954 (Box 26, Folder 179)
    - United States - University of California - Ethical Value Research, 1954 (Box 26, Folder 180)
    - United States - University of California - (F-Ma), 1954 (Box 26, Folder 181)
    - United States - University of California - (Me-Y), 1954 (Box 26, Folder 182)
    - United States - University of Chicago - (A-I), 1954 (Box 26, Folder 183)
    - United States - University of Chicago - (J-Mc), 1954 (Box 26, Folder 184)
    - United States - University of Chicago - (Mac-Mo), 1954 (Box 27, Folder 185)
    - United States - University of Chicago - (P-W), 1954 (Box 27, Folder 186)
    - United States - University - (Ci-L), 1954 (Box 27, Folder 187)
    - United States - University - (M), 1954 (Box 27, Folder 188)
    - United States - University - (N-P), 1954 (Box 27, Folder 189)
    - United States - University of Rochester - (A-D), 1954 (Box 27, Folder 190)
    - United States - University of Rochester - (E-W), 1954 (Box 28, Folder 191)
    - United States - University - (S-V), 1954 (Box 28, Folder 192)
    - United States - University of Washington - (A-Z), 1954 (Box 28, Folder 193)
    - United States - University of Wisconsin - (A-Z), 1954 (Box 28, Folder 194)
    - United States - (V), 1954 (Box 28, Folder 195)
    - United States - (Wa), 1954 (Box 28, Folder 196)
    - United States - (We-Williams), 1954 (Box 28, Folder 197)
    - United States - Williamsburg Restoration - (A-Z), 1954 (Box 29, Folder 198)
    - United States - (Williamson - Wrong), 1954 (Box 29, Folder 199)
    - United States - Yahkub, T. - Yale Council, 1954 (Box 29, Folder 200)
    - United States - Yale University - (A-H), 1954 (Box 29, Folder 201)
    - United States - Yale University - (K-Z), 1954 (Box 29, Folder 202)
    - United States - (Ye-Yo), 1954 (Box 29, Folder 203)
    - United States - Insect Repellents -Van Petten, A.A., 1954 (Box 51, Folder 339)
    - United States - Medical Sciences, 1954; 1954/200.A
      - United States - (A-D), 1954 (Box 29, Folder 204)
      - United States - (H-S), 1954 (Box 29, Folder 205)
      - United States - Tulane University - Medical School, 1954 (Box 30, Folder 206)
      - United States - (U), 1954 (Box 30, Folder 207)
      - United States - University - (A-M), 1954 (Box 30, Folder 208)
      - United States - University - (N-W), 1954 (Box 30, Folder 209)
      - United States -(W), 1954 (Box 30, Folder 210)
    - United States - Nursing, 1954; 1954/200.C
      - United States - (D-Y), 1954 (Box 30, Folder 211)
    - United States - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1954; 1954/200.D
      - United States, 1954 (Box 30, Folder 212)
    - United States - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1954; 1954/200.E
      - United States - (A-Z), 1954 (Box 30, Folder 212)
    - United States - Humanities and Arts, 1954; 1954/200.R
      - United States - (C-P), 1954 (Box 31, Folder 213)
      - United States - (R-W), 1954 (Box 31, Folder 214)
    - United States - Social Sciences, 1954; 1954/200.S
      - United States - (A-F), 1954 (Box 31, Folder 215)
      - United States - (M-A), 1954 (Box 31, Folder 216)
      - United States - (S), 1954 (Box 31, Folder 217)
      - United States - (U-University of Chicago), 1954 (Box 31, Folder 218)
      - United States - (University of Illinois - W), 1954 (Box 31, Folder 219)
  - Alaska, 1954; 1954/202
    - Alaska, 1954 (Box 32, Folder 220)
    - Alaska - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1954; 1954/202.D
      - Alaska, 1954 (Box 32, Folder 220)
    - Alaska - Declinations, 1954; 1954/202.F
      - Alaska, 1954 (Box 32, Folder 220)
  - California, 1954; 1954/205
    - California, 1954 (Box 32, Folder 220)
  - Florida, 1954; 1954/211
    - Florida, 1954 (Box 32, Folder 220)
  - Guam, 1954; 1954/213
    - Guam, 1954 (Box 32, Folder 221)
  - Hawaii, 1954; 1954/214
    - Hawaii, 1954 (Box 32, Folder 221)
    - Hawaii - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1954; 1954/214.D
      - Hawaii, 1954 (Box 32, Folder 222)
    - Hawaii - Declinations, 1954; 1954/214.F
      - Hawaii, 1954 (Box 32, Folder 222)
  - Kentucky, 1954; 1954/220
    - Kentucky, 1954 (Box 32, Folder 222)
  - Massachusetts, 1954; 1954/224
    - Massachusetts, 1954 (Box 32, Folder 222)
  - New York, 1954; 1954/235
    - New York, 1954 (Box 32, Folder 222)
  - Philippines, 1954; 1954/242
    - Philippine Republic, 1954 (Box 32, Folder 223)
    - Philippines - Medical Sciences, 1954; 1954/242.A
      - Philippine Republic, 1954 (Box 32, Folder 224)
    - Philippines - Nursing, 1954; 1954/242.C
      - Philippine Republic, 1954 (Box 32, Folder 224)
    - Philippines - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1954; 1954/242.E
      - Philippine Republic, 1954 (Box 32, Folder 224)
    - Philippines - Declinations, 1954; 1954/242.F
      - Philippine Republic, 1954 (Box 32, Folder 224)
    - Philippines - Malaria, 1954; 1954/242.I
      - Philippine Republic, 1954 (Box 32, Folder 224)
    - Philippines - Humanities and Arts, 1954; 1954/242.R
      - Philippine Republic, 1954 (Box 32, Folder 224)
  - Puerto Rico, 1954; 1954/243
    - Puerto Rico, 1954 (Box 32, Folder 225)
    - Puerto Rico - Medical Sciences, 1954; 1954/243.A
      - Puerto Rico, 1954 (Box 33, Folder 226)
    - Puerto Rico - Nursing, 1954; 1954/243.C
      - Puerto Rico, 1954 (Box 33, Folder 226)
    - Puerto Rico - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1954; 1954/243.E
      - Puerto Rico, 1954 (Box 33, Folder 226)
    - Puerto Rico - Declinations, 1954; 1954/243.F
      - Puerto Rico, 1954 (Box 33, Folder 226)
    - Puerto Rico - Social Sciences, 1954; 1954/243.S
      - Puerto Rico, 1954 (Box 33, Folder 226)
  - Virgin Islands, 1954; 1954/257
    - Virgin Islands - Declinations, 1954; 1954/257.F
      - Virgin Islands, 1954 (Box 33, Folder 227)
  - Trust Territory of the Pacific Islands, 1954; 1954/258
    - Trust Territory of the Pacific Islands - Nursing, 1954; 1954/258.C
      - Trust Territory of the Pacific Islands, 1954 (Box 33, Folder 227)
  - South America, 1954; 1954/300
    - South America and Latin America - Administration - (January - March), 1954 (Box 33, Folder 228)
    - South America and Latin America - Administration - (April-June), 1954 (Box 33, Folder 228)
    - South America and Latin America - Administration - (April-June), 1954 (Box 33, Folder 229)
    - South America and Latin America - Administration - (July-September), 1954 (Box 33, Folder 230)
    - (October-December), 1954 (Box 33, Folder 231)
    - South American and Latin America - (I-P), 1954 (Box 33, Folder 232)
    - South America - Medical Sciences, 1954; 1954/300.A
      - South American and Latin America, 1954 (Box 34, Folder 233)
    - South America - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1954; 1954/300.E
      - South American and Latin America, 1954 (Box 34, Folder 233)
    - South America - Social Sciences, 1954; 1954/300.S
      - South American and Latin America, 1954 (Box 34, Folder 233)
  - Argentina, 1954; 1954/301
    - Argentina, 1954 (Box 34, Folder 233)
    - Argentina - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1954; 1954/301.D
      - Argentina, 1954 (Box 34, Folder 233)
    - Argentina - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1954; 1954/301.E
      - Argentina, 1954 (Box 34, Folder 233)
  - Bolivia, 1954; 1954/303
    - Bolivia, 1954 (Box 34, Folder 233)
    - Bolivia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1954; 1954/303.E
      - Bolivia, 1954 (Box 34, Folder 234)
  - Brazil, 1954; 1954/305
    - Brazil - (A-H), 1954 (Box 34, Folder 234)
    - Brazil - (I-J), 1954 (Box 34, Folder 235)
    - Brazil - (K-N), 1954 (Box 34, Folder 236)
    - Brazil - (O-T), 1954 (Box 34, Folder 237)